let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is C++?",
    answer: "C++ supports both procedural and object oriented programming language",
    options: [
      "C++ is an object oriented programming language",
      "C++ is a procedural programming language",
      "C++ supports both procedural and object oriented programming language",
      "C++ is a functional programming language"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is the correct syntax of including a user defined header files in C++?",
    answer: "#include “userdefined”",
    options: [
      "#include [userdefined]",
      "#include “userdefined”",
      "#include userdefined.h",
      "#include userdefined"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is used for comments in C++?",
    answer: "both // comment or /* comment */",
    options: [
      "/* comment */",
      "// comment */",
      "// comment",
      "both // comment or /* comment */"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of Constructor in C++?",
    answer: "Friend constructor",
    options: [
      "Default constructor",
      "Parameterized constructor",
      "Copy constructor",
      "Friend constructor"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following type is provided by C++ but not C?",
    answer: "bool",
    options: [
      "bool",
      "double",
      "float",
      "int"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following correctly declares an array in C++?",
    answer: "int array[10];",
    options: [
      "int array;",
      "array{10};",
      "array array[10];",
      "int array[10];"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which is more effective while calling the C++ functions?",
    answer: "call by reference",
    options: [
      "call by object",
      "call by pointer",
      "call by value",
      "call by reference"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is Inheritance in C++?",
    answer: "Deriving new classes from existing classes",
    options: [
      "Deriving new classes from existing classes",
      "Overloading of classes",
      "Classes with same names",
      "Wrapping of data into a single class"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is meant by a polymorphism in C++?",
    answer: "class having many forms",
    options: [
      "class having only single form",
      "class having four forms",
      "class having many forms",
      "class having two forms"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following constructors are provided by the C++ compiler if not defined in a class?",
    answer: "All of the mentioned",
    options: [
      "Copy constructor",
      "Default constructor",
      "Assignment constructor",
      "All of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
];